<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en_us"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/muse2/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/muse2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en_us" /><updated>2022-03-22T02:39:39+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/muse2/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Mihee</title><author><name>Sal</name></author><entry><title type="html">Code</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/muse2/is-intelligence-enough/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Code" /><published>2019-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/muse2/is-intelligence-enough</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/muse2/is-intelligence-enough/"><![CDATA[<p>Education must also train one for quick, resolute and effective thinking. To think incisively and to think for one’s self is very difficult.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>We are prone to let our mental life become invaded by legions of half truths, prejudices, and propaganda. At this point, I often wonder whether or not education is fulfilling its purpose. A great majority of the so-called educated people do not think logically and scientifically.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Even the press, the classroom, the platform, and the pulpit in many instances do not give us objective and unbiased truths. To save man from the morass of propaganda, in my opinion, is one of the chief aims of education. Education must enable one to sift and weigh evidence, to discern the true from the false, the real from the unreal, and the facts from the fiction.</p>

<p>The function of education, therefore, is to teach one to think intensively and to think critically. But education which stops with efficiency may prove the greatest menace to society. The most dangerous criminal may be the man gifted with reason, but with no morals.</p>

<p>The late Eugene Talmadge, in my opinion, possessed one of the better minds of Georgia, or even America. Moreover, he wore the Phi Beta Kappa key. By all measuring rods, Mr. Talmadge could think critically and intensively; yet he contends that I am an inferior being. Are those the types of men we call educated?</p>

<p>We must remember that intelligence is not enough. Intelligence plus character–that is the goal of true education. The complete education gives one not only power of concentration, but worthy objectives upon which to concentrate. The broad education will, therefore, transmit to one not only the accumulated knowledge of the race but also the accumulated experience of social living.</p>]]></content><author><name>Mihee Lee</name></author><category term="MUSE-VAE" /><category term="code" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Education must also train one for quick, resolute and effective thinking. To think incisively and to think for one’s self is very difficult.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/muse2/assets/images/5.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/muse2/assets/images/5.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Dataset</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/muse2/tree-of-codes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dataset" /><published>2018-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/muse2/tree-of-codes</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/muse2/tree-of-codes/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="path-finding-simulation-dataset-pfsd">Path Finding Simulation Dataset (PFSD)</h2>

<ul>
  <li>
    <p>Path Finding Simulation Dataset was generated by simulating the navigation of agents within 100 large synthetic environments.
These environments were designed according to the external shapes and interior organizations of rooms and corridors generally found in contemporary architecture.
Unlike SDD and nuScenes, the non-navigable spaces in these environments are significantly more complex for navigation.
Each of the environments was used to simulate 500 scenes (amounting to 50,000 total scenes), where a single agent navigates between two random points within the environment using the prevalent Social Force model.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>The scenes were sampled at 2.5 Hz and further divided into training/val/test cases with 3.2s (8 frames) of observed trajectories and 4.8s (12 frames) of future trajectories.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>We use subset of the PFSD and make the train/val/test set with 40/2/4 different synthetic environments, respectively. It is the binary map consisting of navigable (white-colored) and non-navigable (black-colored) space of the entire environment of one scenario. An agent finds a path by moving from a room to another room using the exit between obstacles.</p>
  </li>
</ul>

<h2 id="download-pfsd">Download PFSD</h2>

<p><strong><a href="">Raw data</a></strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Wm5CTBrxozg9zMKvS2l9M3XtHhWyy3g9/view?usp=sharing">Preprocessed data for MUSE-VAE</a></strong></p>]]></content><author><name>Mihee Lee</name></author><category term="MUSE-VAE" /><category term="PFSD" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Path Finding Simulation Dataset (PFSD)]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/muse2/assets/images/8.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/muse2/assets/images/8.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>